Inkyu Shin | Curriculum Vitae

☑ dlsrbgg33@kaist.ac.kr

I am a second-year Ph.D. student at Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) under the co-supervision of Prof. Kuk-Jin Yoon and Prof. In So Kweon. I earned my B.S and M.S degrees in automotive engineering from Hanyang University(HYU) and KAIST in 2019 and 2021. I interned at NEC Laboratories America, Inc, San Jose, CA (with Dr. Yi-Hsuan Tsai), and Google Research (with Dr. Liang-Chieh Chen, and Dr. Jun Xie; expected 2022)

Research Interests

My research interests currently lie in computer vision. Specifically, I pursue the goal of effectively processing data and building strong recognition model in computer vision. Followings are my main research topics.

- Semantic Segmentation
- Domain Adaptation and Generalization
- Simulated Learning
- Self-supervised Learning

Ultimately, the purpose of these researches is to apply to a variety of applications (e.g., Autonomous driving, Robot Navigation, AR/VR).

Research Experience

0	Google Research Student Researcher, Mentors: Liang-Chieh Chen and Jun Xie	LA, CA (virtual) May 2022 - April 2023
0	NEC Laboratories America, Inc Research Intern, Mentors: Yi-Hsuan Tsai	San Jose, CA (virtual) May 2021 - Aug 2021
0	Korea University Research Intern, Supervisor: Jaegul Choo	Seoul, Korea Sep 2018 - Dec 2018
0	Hanyang University Research Assistant, Supervisor: Myuong-Ho Sunwoo	Seoul, Korea Jul 2018 - Aug 2018
0	Samsung Electronics Intern, Semi-conductor Test Group.	Hwasung, Korea Jan 2018 - Mar 2018

Education

0	Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Future Vehicle Ph.D. degree, Co-Advisors: Kuk-Jin Yoon and In So Kweon	Daejeon, Korea 2021-
0	Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Future Vehicle M.S degree, Advisor: In So Kweon Master's Thesis: Learning to Scale the Labels for Self-training based Domain Adaptation	Daejeon, Korea 2019-2021
0	Hanyang University (HYU) AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING B.S degree	Seoul, Korea 2013-2019

Publications

(C: conference / J: journal / P: preprint / * :equal contributions)

International Conference.....

 [C7] MM-TTA: Multi-Modal Test-Time Adaptation for 3D Semantic Segmentation Inkyu Shin, Yi-Hsuan Tsai, Bingbing Zhuang, Samuel Schulter, Buyu Liu, Sparsh Garg, In So Kweon, Kuk-Jin Yoon
 Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022

- [C6] UDA-COPE: Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Category-level Object Pose Estimation
 Taeyeop Lee, Byeong-Uk Lee, Inkyu Shin, Jaesung Choe, Ukcheol Shin, In So Kweon, Kuk-Jin Yoon
 Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [P2] Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Video Semantic Segmentation Kwanyong Park*, Inkyu Shin*, Sanghyun Woo, In So Kweon arXiv, 2021
- o [C5] LabOR: Labeling Only if Required for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation Inkyu Shin, Dong-Jin Kim, Jae Won Cho, Sanghyun Woo, Kwanyong Park, In So Kweon International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2021 (Oral)
 - Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2021.
- [P1] Learning Representations by Contrasting Clusters While Bootstrapping Instances
 Junsoo Lee, Hojoon Lee, Inkyu Shin, Jaekyoung Bae, In So Kweon, Jaegul Choo
 arXiv, 2020
- [C4] Discover, Hallucinate, and Adapt:
 Open Compound Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation
 Kwanyong Park, Sanghyun Woo, Inkyu Shin, In So Kweon
 Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2020

 Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2021.
- [C3] Two-phase Pseudo Label Densification for Self-training based Domain Adaptation Inkyu Shin, Sanghyun Woo, Fei pan, In So Kweon European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020
 - Also presented at "Visual Learning with Limited Labels" Workshops in conjunction with (CVPR), 2020
- [C2] Unsupervised Intra-domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation through Self-Supervision
 Fei pan, Inkyu Shin, Francois Rameau, Seokju Lee, In So Kweon
 Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2020 (Oral)
 - Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2020.
- [C1] Image-to-Image Translation via Group-wise Deep Whitening-and-Coloring Transformation Wonwoong Cho, Sungha Choi, David Keetae Park, Inkyu Shin, Jaegul Choo Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2019 (Oral)

Awards

- o 2021: Qualcomm Inovation Award.
- o 2020: Qualcomm Inovation Award.

IT skills

- \circ Languages: Python, MATLAB, C, LATEX
- o Libraries: PyTorch, TensorFlow

References

- In So Kweon, Professor, KAIST iskweon@kaist.ac.kr
- Kuk-Jin Yoon, Professor, KAIST kjyoon@kaist.ac.kr

Service

o Military Service: Graduated from US Army Sergeant school(WLC) as KATUSA.